kidnapping assassination and a london
shootout inside the ca cia's secret war
plans are against wikileaks but it
sounds to me more like cia's secret war
plans against julian assange there's
plenty to talk about i'm political
analyst garland nixon and i'm former cia
officer john kiriakou let's talk about
julian assange
[Music]
well john it looks like captain russia
gate michael isikoff has been up to his
old shenanigans he wrote a story um and
uh it was the cia's secret war plans
against and he didn't even say who it
was really against he said it was
against wikileaks he had to
de-personalize it it wasn't against a
man who is a journalist
i've read the story it's a bit of a long
story a lot going on in that you john
your thoughts
why don't we do this for people who may
not have read the story or maybe kind of
just heard a bit about it why don't you
kind of fill in the blanks what did we
find out here
well we found out that mike pompeo when
he was the cia director was
not just actively involved in
in pursuing
what was either an assassination attempt
or an attempt to kidnap julian assange
in london but he was the driving force
behind this this plan this was a covert
action uh plan which requires the
president's signature on something
called a presidential finding it has to
go through the justice department it has
to go through the uh the lawyers on the
national security council then to the
national security adviser before making
its way to the president and this plan
was so crazy as to defy any logic what
it was
was uh the cia was prepared
working with british intelligence mi6
to engage in a shootout in front of the
ecuadorian embassy in the knightsbridge
section of london now if any of our
viewers have been to knightsbridge
that's where herod's department store is
it's
it's literally the nicest shopping
district in the world it's like having a
shootout
at fifth avenue and and east 57th street
uh it's it's insane to even contemplate
uh a secondary plan that they had was in
the event that julian actually made it
out of the ecuadorian embassy and onto a
plane
presumably a russian diplomatic plane
uh the plan was to shoot the tires of
the plane out so that it couldn't take
off now that's an act of war it's a
violation of international treaties but
this this crazy plan
uh went all the way up to the president
before at some point it was killed it it
is crazy to me that
donald trump may have been the adult in
the room to say that this was too much
it was more likely the national security
adviser
but uh you know if there were any doubts
at all either either in the minds of
people who aren't necessarily supportive
of julian assange or in the mind of the
judge who um
who criticized julian assange despite
ordering that he not be extradited to
the united states this ought to put any
doubts to rest
well the other thing is this i feel like
as soon as i see isakoff and i see the
word russian anywhere i'm suspicious you
know i look at it and you don't know i
mean you know there's some truth in this
story but you don't know how much is
embellished and how much is window
dressing and i just feel like they had
to put in there oh and by the way the
russians might have wanted to sneak them
out of the country yeah they're still
still trying to wait yeah they're in a
way they're pushing that julian assange
work with the russians that's already
been debunked but they know that most
people don't dig deep enough to know
that that's right that's right mike
isikoff you know used to be a serious uh
investigative journalist he he was with
the the washington post the new york
times um he's a pulitzer prize winner he
was the the lead investigative
journalist at newsweek
now he's at yahoo news this is supposed
to be a serious guy but he did himself
real damage serious damage to his
reputation by not just latching on to
the russiagate narrative when it was
debunked
rather than correct himself he doubled
down on russiagate he also was one of
the early authors uh to to publish a
book about russiagate and then went on
to have the entire book debunked so it's
kind of hard to believe what he what he
has to say with that said
um he co-wrote this piece with two other
yahoo news reporters and they say that
they interviewed 30 former cia officers
and white house staff members um with
everybody telling the same story um i
believe it
we know mike pompeo we know mike pompeo
has no respect for the law we know that
mike pompeo had an obsession with
wikileaks and julian assange because of
the revelations that came out of the
vault seven uh documents
i i think mike pompeo tried to kill
julian assange
i think you're right let's look at the
story right here and this is the part
that freaks me out
it says uh pompeo was seeking revenge
that's one part of it and then when you
go to the blast it says basically over
they were so embarrassed over vault
seven they were seeing blood seeking
revenge seeing blood that's not about
professionalism that's not about the law
that's about i'm going i have an enemy
and i have the ability to attack them to
kill them i have the ability to use
violence you know what that is that's
tony soprano right there yeah when i
hear someone say you know what this guy
did something and i don't like him and i
want to whack him that's you know what i
mean i started thinking of words like
bonanno and lucie and luciano that's
what i started thinking about the man is
acts uh it seems to me that he ran the
cia and the state department like a
crime boss
yeah uh that that's exactly right and
you know he was very very unpopular
among cia people too for a couple of
reasons
first was that he
he participated in six different
bible study groups a week at the cia so
rather than being in his office actually
running the cia like he was supposed to
be doing he was busy praying with six
different
uh evangelical bible study groups
he also had this weird habit of signing
all of his official correspondence with
have a blessed day
that's just not something that's that's
done at the cia you know sure there are
a lot of religious people like there are
anywhere but keep it to yourself you got
a job to do so people were generally
happy to see him go he didn't leave a
good impression at the cia
you know another thing in here i'll have
i'll find it but and this i found very
very troubling
one of the most troubling things here
but it was a branch off of what happened
to assange anyway if you read this story
you'll find that they considered and
discussed taking action against other
journalists yes
glenn greenwald i think was laura is
there a pointless
yeah yeah talk about your thoughts what
are your thoughts on that you know in
the whole article was a very long
article but this to me was the most
frightening part of it
none of us should be surprised that the
cia and mike pompeo were going after
julian assange but to equate major
investigative journalists with
what they call information brokers
would open up national security
journalists to espionage charges just
for doing journalism
you know there's been an ongoing problem
garland with the mainstream media not
supporting julian assange you never read
articles about julian in the washington
post or the new york times you never
hear about him on cnn or msnbc
and rarely even on fox
but um
but what's really dangerous is that if
people don't line up behind julian if
they don't
support julian's right to publish
then they're next logically that's
really what what the white house uh
wants to do and i don't just mean the
donald trump white house i mean this
goes back to george w bush barack obama
went after journalists donald trump
certainly did joe biden hasn't changed
the policy at all this is something that
all journalists should be
afraid of
and you know to me and i don't know if
you see it this way but i see it this
way i've been saying this for a while
this is the war on terror coming home
this is
20 years of people getting accustomed to
go to another country and you violate
their laws you violate their rules you
violate when you get in that other
country there are no laws it's a
battlefield you can do anything you want
to right right the problem is you get
accustomed to that and whenever they
feel threatened whether it's julian
assange or it's garland nixon john
kiriakou someone jimmy dore whoever did
they get accustomed to operating in an
environment where there's no rule let me
tell you something real quick that i was
a cop from you know i retired 20 some
years right right and one of the things
and i'm going to admit it one of the
things i got accustomed to was not
paying any attention to the rules when
you're a cop you're pulling over here
you got they go say call the we need you
to check on this you put over this way
you barely use your blinker people get
out of your way even when your lights
are not on you're flipping around to go
this array that direction whatever right
and you get accustomed to paying no
attention to the um traffic signals
because you're doing stuff you're
responding to [__] right right and once
i retired i had to get my i kept getting
pulled over by cops
because i was like turning them pulling
a stop sign screw this go this way that
way and you're they pull you over and i
show my badge and i say look i just
retired and they'd be like
i understand they can't have that
problem on the weekends when i'm out but
but i say that's a long version of
saying this
the war on terror has produced a
government that is accustomed to acting
in a lawless manner first in one iraq
when they invaded it then libya then
they expanded it if africom they
expanded into more and more countries
and it's coming home and now they're
acting lawlessness in england and if
they're doing it in england you know
they're doing it right here in the
united states and that's the crazy part
of this garland this isn't you know
we're not talking about doing it in the
streets of kabul or khartoum or sana
we're talking about knightsbridge london
here we're talking about the british
agreeing to be the lead in the shootout
we're talking about a shootout in a
civilian neighborhood right an upscale
very upscale neighborhood we're also
talking about the murder of an
australian citizen not some terrorist
from afghanistan or pakistan or whatever
an australian national australia is a
five-eyes country
the five eyes countries are the us uk
canada australia and new zealand they
share all their intelligence they they
don't recruit each other's citizens they
don't do operations on each other's soil
unless they're joint operations but to
murder
or kidnap a five eyes
citizen tells me that the australians
were also involved in this
well here's the other part let's be
square about this
if they were
knowingly unwittingly if we're honest
about ourself and this is coming out
it's becoming blatantly obvious obvious
as um joe biden continues with um donald
trump's america first craziness right
if you are there are no allies to the
u.s empire you're a vassal of
convenience yes and um let's face it i
don't know how familiar you are with it
but the united states basically
overthrew the government of australia in
1975 and replaced the replace the prime
minister yeah um so the reality is if
you look what happened with france
lately what did france learned france
learned that
that the u.s empire and its vassal
states
is a hierarchy and france you ain't at
the top of the hierarchy they just learn
that so i think part of it what you're
saying
is also part of
um what i think is the weakening of the
us as the world hegemon there are a
number of cracks in the dam but i think
one of the cracks in the dam
are the um
the other countries like europe and
australia waking up to figure out where
am i in this hierarchy and am i
comfortable with where i am in this
hierarchy right and the hierarchy keeps
changing i mean the last couple of years
anyway there have been a lot of changes
and i i'm glad at least that there was
somebody at some point and i'm thinking
it probably was the national security
adviser whoever
i was gonna say would have been there
were so many of them under donald trump
um
it would have been um
wasn't mattis was it no no mattis was
sex
but it would have been at the same time
uh with mattis uh
but anyway yeah there there had to be
somebody to say wait a minute stop this
is crazy it's not like we're trying to
take out you know ayman zawahiri
in some cave somewhere right this is
this is julian assange
in uh in knightsbridge london
and then you know you're going to
eventually have to answer to to courts
there's going to be a federal judge who
says uh well did you go through the the
process to extradite him to the united
states and at that point the answer was
no
they hadn't they just decided ah we're
just gonna start a shootout in the
streets and we're just gonna kill him
and if we can't kill him we'll shoot the
plane and the other part of it is
and
and this is what i think is dangerous i
thought it was bad with that guy there
was a guy that named i think is he from
chicago i think his name was padilla and
they yeah
him as a as basically they read they
came up with a new classification for
him they said you go under this
classification therefore you have no
constitutional rights yeah he was an
enemy combatant and they put him in a
navy brig in charleston south carolina
and he appealed and went all the way to
up to the supreme court and the supreme
court said tough luck you're an enemy
combatant exactly and that i think that
was a bad thing for this reason because
here um they decided to call what was it
they were going to call um information
brokers they were going to call glenn
greenwald and others and the person who
made the document about snowden and so
what we found and this is just a
bastardization of of law
hey
i can't assassinate or do you take this
um extra judicial action against the
citizen i'll just come up with a new
name i'll call him a fig womb he's a fig
womp and according to this law that i
just wrote fig it's open season on fig
womb's boom take him out and that's all
they're doing they're like there's no
legal way that we can assassinate this
guy for what he did especially when he
hasn't been convicted of doing anything
wrong and guess what you're gonna have
to start assassinating people with the
new york times the one opposed to the
guardian because they all put it out too
and the dangerous part is whether it's
garland nixon or
glenn greenwald or assange all we got to
do is come up with a new name a
definition for that new name and then
determine the state then what laws what
rights what whatever applies to that new
name that's then you have no
constitution if you can simply
reclassify citizens or human beings as
something that's outside of the law yeah
and let me tell you how this works
bureaucratically somebody at the cia in
this case apparently it was uh mike
pompeo comes up up with an idea to uh to
carry out an assassination against the
likes of julian assange so they put it
in this very specific format and they
send it from the cia to the to the
justice department's office of legal
counsel olc the notorious office of
legal counsel where john you was what
exactly exactly john you and jay bybee
during the bush administration now the
problem with olc is they're supposed to
be the deep thinkers
at justice they're supposed to be the
ones to tell the cia whether something
is legal or illegal but they wrecked
their reputation by justifying the
torture program by justifying
international
extraordinary renditions by justifying a
secret prison system and so what they do
is they'll come up with the craziest
unlikeliest legal interpretation
to declare legal whatever it is the cia
wants them to declare legal
and once they sign off on it it goes to
the team of lawyers in the general
counsel's office of the national
security council so once those lawyers
chop on it and then they they meet with
the cia's lawyers to to come up with
acceptable language in this thing for
everybody then it goes to the national
security advisor for a signature once
the national security advisor approves
of it it goes to the president they make
a clean copy they call it a presidential
finding the president signs it
and then copies go to the office of the
director of national intelligence to the
national security advisor to the
director of the cia and to the
operations
center of the cia where it's kept in a
safe
what you might have noticed
is nowhere in that whole
scenario
does it ever get before a judge
and in many cases
it won't even get before the oversight
committees now here's the real
you know turd in the room
anytime there is a covert action program
it has to be briefed to the oversight
committees because the oversight
committees have to authorize it in the
form of an authorization bill
and they have to fund it through a
top secret appropriations bill now
they'll bury it somewhere in the in the
defense budget so nobody notices it
uh
but
if the cia deems that the operation is
counter intelligence in nature
and 99 times out of 100 that's dealing
with a mole inside the cia maybe there's
a russian mole a chinese mole whatever
then they don't have to brief it to the
hill
so all they had to do is say the magic
words
that wikileaks is a non-state hostile
intelligence service
you know
people didn't really make much when mike
pompeo said that in public they said oh
pompeo it's not an intelligence service
why is he saying something that like
that he did it on purpose
that was a signal
that we're not going to the oversight
committees with this
and that's what happened the oversight
committees didn't know anything about
this operation yeah and and and um when
we look at it the other part of it is
this
it wasn't it was a acknowledgement
when you read it it's obvious that
um and i think it actually says it in
there that basically um pompeo really
could care less about the law
he didn't care he didn't care concerned
it was dog garnered he'd it was that
george w bush cowboy mindset it was that
nixon if the guy if the president does
this it's not illegal and he had gotten
to that arrogant machiavellian really
um autocratic totalitarian mindset
that people who get power they get drunk
with the power and then they begin to
believe that they're doing good
so that it doesn't matter the law is for
our lessers the law are sort of little
the littles down there because we're the
good guys they convince themselves
they're the good guys so they can do
whatever they want yeah
and i i was a cop i saw that on a small
scale you know i'm sure you saw it on a
large sale i as a cop i saw it on a
small scale in that
i knew and listened to the discussion
you know the locker room discussion of
cops and you hear that stuff you hear
the kind of conversations you hear
people who refer to yeah you know i came
out there was a couple of dirt bags
standing on the corner a couple of d
what they're saying is basically the
people in the community a dirt bag
they're not human beings they're just a
couple of those other things there so
once you become men to think like that
that you're better than they are their
lives aren't valuable they have no
rights they're dirt bags they're not
human beings and and you see that
mindset i saw it in law enforcement i'm
sure you saw it in the things that you
did and what happens is that's when
people wander off into crazy land and
they get to where mike pompeo was here
and to be honest
just
trying to do this just coming to the
white house with this
should have been enough to say this guy
can't be cia anymore and he can't hold
any other position he's a dangerous man
you are exactly right you know when i
was when i was still working at the cia
and for those of you who think i'm still
in the cia shame on you
uh but when i was at the when i was at
the cia we received a cable from a large
overseas station asking permission to
carry out an assassination
this is immediately post 911
and uh i was the morning briefer for the
the director and the deputy directors
and so i briefed it i said we we have
this cable in from so and so and they're
asking for permission to uh to carry out
an assassination i had never seen a
cable like this before i had never seen
anything in writing ever asking for
permission to kill somebody
the deputy director for operations was
so appalled that someone would put this
in writing he instructed me not to
respond to the cable and i said well i
mean he's going to call right the person
who wrote the cable is going to call and
ask what's going on and he said either
don't take the call or when he calls
tell him he's an idiot
and hang up on him well he got the
message he never he never called we just
never responded to the cable but then to
be so bold and so and so
over the top
to actually come up with a plan
to murder julian assange and then to
brief it so widely
that 30 people are willing to go to a to
a journalist and um and confirm it
i if i had been president i would have
fired pompeo on the spot well yeah
chicken patty makes a good point and
that is pompeo admitted cia lied cheated
and stole but he left out the murder
part but i think that came apart okay
you know that just came with it but the
thing about it is
you know when pompeo said that i've
never heard anybody say that before you
know when pompeo said that and laughed
about it in a sociopathic kind of way
and i i gotta be honest i look you know
no i'm no psychologist i read the
sociopath next door you know i mean i
did too
great look oh my gosh yeah i love doing
i've read
rally bought it for me yeah awesome book
it is and but you know based on my
limited knowledge it wouldn't shock me
if i compared the standards for a
sociopath and that i saw you know and i
looked in that book and there was a
picture of mike you know mike pompeo
with the arrow pointing like right
listen man they're all sociopaths yes
a cia psychiatrist once told me that the
cia actively seeks to hire people who
have sociopathic tendencies
not sociopaths because sociopaths are
impossible to control right they have no
conscience and they just blow right
through the the polygraph exam because
they're unable to feel remorse or regret
the thing is is that the cia is like you
know a fortune 500 company where the
sociopaths slip through the cracks and
they rise to the top to these leadership
positions for the exact reason that
they're willing to step on the backs of
everybody around them to make their way
to the top and then once they make their
way to the top
they fall into that same pattern of not
thinking that the rules apply to them
and uh and they're perfectly willing to
carry out crimes against humanity or or
war crimes
well you know look one of the things
that you read and i'll name two names
and then when i saw them boy i'm not
saying they're sociopaths i'm just
saying my eyes bugged out what happens
fiona hill you know who that is
oh sure the another one is um
uh flower noir hillary's girl
yeah yeah both
when i looked at them
and i saw
that jaw
that is there's no smiles there there's
no emotion there it's
and the dead shark eyes those great
white eyes just before he clamps down on
you you know just before he bites that
seal in half those dead shark eyes
there's no life in them and i looked at
him and i'm like oh my god so i
understand what you're saying because
when i see the neocons neo pecan is just
oh my god you know yeah and i and
there's just so many of them you know
when they had that ukraine hearing and
they start marching the um you know the
the fiona hills and these kind of people
through one after one
and i'm looking at these people and i'm
like man that person right there hasn't
had a happy feeling in their life since
1977. yep there is some scary stuff
you've got that right hey may i respond
garland 2 to coop w uh who writes why
would the cia allow their agents to be
friends with someone who sold them out
you would think you would be the last
guy that had current intel or am i
missing something you're missing a whole
lot uh first of all i didn't sell
anybody out i
called out the cia for violating both
u.s and international law second you
make a very broad assumption that that
i'm unpopular at the cia
70 cia officers signed a letter to
president obama asking him to pardon me
because there are a lot of people at the
cia who believe that the cia should work
within the confines of the law
and so i'm in touch with a whole lot of
cia people on a daily basis you you have
a view of the cia in your mind that's
just simply incorrect
yeah i mean we know and we know people
so many people uh ray mcgovern i think
phil giraldi is indeed former ceo
giraldi you spent 32 years as a cia
officer yes yeah so we know a number of
people they can look up what is it
veteran intelligence uh professionals
for san antonio
yeah so there are a lot of people out
here and again you know you know and
i'll say this i mean i'm going to get
straight too far but i deal with the
same thing like being ex-cop where
people are like you're a law enforcement
officer how can i trust you you're
probably reporting everything back to
them
you have nothing better to do with your
time yeah i'm retired they're not paying
me anymore but i'm doing it just for the
good of the order you know i think i was
a pain in the neck to them when i was
there that's right i know i was they
were probably happy to see me go
but at any rate looking at this um the
other thing is
uh looking at this and you always got to
call out the media and that is yes this
should be a number two things
this should be the number one story for
a week but number two
in a just society
which this it clearly isn't
there would have to be congressional
hearings there would have to be the
congressional oversight board calling in
these 30 people seeing if someone needs
to be prosecuted ensuring that they
see if the rules need to be changed i
mean whatever but there should be like a
gigantic both house and senate hearing
the tell here is
the the tell that there is no truly no
oversight over the cia is
congress ain't saying a word not a
single word garland this is such an
important point that you're making i i
looked specifically
for
statements any statements by people who
are supposed to be
on the right side on these issues like
for example senator dianne feinstein
former chairwoman of the senate
intelligence committee or senator ron
wyden the the progressive democrat from
oregon
these are the people we're supposed to
turn to
to make sure that the cia operates
within the confines of the law not a
single word not from any of the
democrats on either the senate committee
or the house committee nothing
and add this
here's what makes it even more
conspicuous i'm not going to say oh
they're not doing their jobs or oh
they're selling or oh they're blah blah
blah conspicuous
you know almost as this behind the
scenes they've made a decision not to
touch it which i kind of think they have
yes
because pompeo was part of the evil
trump regime
so
anything around trump you're supposed to
attack if you're a democrat if you're
blue it should be blood in the water oh
my god look what we found that happened
in the trump regime what we need to do
is find out that it went all the way up
to trump so we can now finally prosecute
trump and pompeo for this and ensure
that in 2024 donald trump can't run
again that's what i would think i would
hear from the democrats if they weren't
bull crapping me
exactly
exactly we're not hearing anything you
know i i've mentioned this before and
forgive me if i'm repeating myself but
when i got out of prison i spent 23
months in prison after blowing the
whistle on the cia's torch program when
i got home i happened to be in a vet
here in washington and senator ron wyden
was at the event and
he was generally a supporter of mine but
when push came to shove you know he
really didn't do anything to to help
he made a couple of nice statements but
didn't really do anything substantive so
i went up to him and i i told him you
know frankly i was i was disappointed i
had expected a little bit more
and he got angry and defensive and he
said look it took everything i had just
to not lose my security clearance
and man that just so crystallized
everything for me
that
even the people who are supposed to be
tough on the cia they just don't have
the guts to open their mouths because
they're going to be stripped of their
access and if they're stripped of their
access then they have nothing in
washington there's no power there's no
authority
they're irrelevant
and what the other part of it is this
and if that happens you know what the
other half is and that is the machine's
going to cut your money out they're
going to rewrite redraw your district
you're out the door if you go about it
so it was that was the thing again that
shows that this is undemocratic that's
right it shows that these are people
that are operating outside of the
constraints of democracy they have
captured democracy so both the
corporations and the intelligence
community but i repeat myself they have
captured democracy in a way that now
um
we use the term democracy that ain't it
if the elected representatives do not
have oversight authority which they
don't if you are being threatened
for the use of your oversight authority
clearly you don't have any then we have
to redefine what this country is because
you know americans are like this is a
democracy and we can reign in there's no
reigning in the inmates truly are
controlling the asylum
you have that right the inmates are
controlling the asylum and it wasn't
always like that you know it tended to
be cyclical where we saw you know
between 1975 and
and about
1993 or 95
that there really was real oversight uh
congress was serious about it they were
intimately involved in the day-to-day
operations of the cia and that that all
began to change in the 90s and then of
course the 911 attacks changed
everything apparently permanently here
we are
20 years later and congressional
oversight is at its weakest point really
since the oversight committees were
created
yeah it's it's we will we can't get
anything like the church committee we
can't get anything really um because um
the
the various what what used to what did
we used to call them we used to call
them special interest groups or interest
groups but we've got a couple of
interest groups that own everything that
have kind of combined to a point where
they're kind of bored on us you know
where they've kind of come together so
much that there's no that is there a
dental delineation when
the the guy who is the new secretary to
the air force of the air force came from
raytheon when the secretary of defense
came from raytheon exactly secretary of
density defense came from raytheon is
there a delineation between our pentagon
and raytheon yes you're exactly right
you know this is what makes things so
ugly here in washington is this
revolving door you know
i disagree with donald trump on 99
of the issues but when he called
washington a swamp he's he was right it
is a swamp um he didn't do anything to
make it better certainly if anything it
got worse under donald trump but there
is this revolving door especially in
defense and national security
between
the big uh weapons manufacturers and uh
and defense and cia
you know the last thing i want to touch
base before we go is i think well
because i don't think this case is on
the up and up the extradition case it is
a it is kabuki theater it's not going to
matter but in the real world
the
discussion about whether julian hassan
should initially come in london was
whether or not he could be executed
because england couldn't ex could not
extradite any uh person to a country
where they could face execution the u.s
oh we won't kill him
then the next discussion was well maybe
he'll kill himself so this that all
about whether or not he'll die i would
argue that now that it has come out that
the u.s intelligence committee's
considered i mean a community is
considered an extrajudicial killing
that there is no way that he should be
extradited to the u.s because
you can have an agreement with the u.s
that they won't um
kill him judicially you can have an
agreement that that that going by the
rules they won't kill them but there's
they have already demonstrated and in
particular when it comes to julian
assange that they have no respect for
the rules so joe biden might say hey i'm
not going to do it trump might be back
in in 2024 or pompeo who the hell ever
and they're like glad we're back hey do
me a favor can you go over there in
epstein julian assange
you know i i have to say that after
after everything that uh
that the um
the judge the british judge what was her
name barrett not
yes um you know she she essentially
mocked
uh uh the idea that julian was in any
danger were he to be extradited to the
united states well now that the case is
is up for appeal
i i think that no british judge in his
or her right mind
would approve of an extradition now
because now the us
the plan for for julian and wikileaks
has been laid bare
it's clear that the guy is just not
going to make it here
john two things think about what has
happened and i wonder
if these things weren't an accident
but to the two things that have happened
is this guy's sega
sigi or whatever his name right right
this guy comes out and basically says up
in iceland everything i said was a lie
i'm sorry my testimony testimony about
assange was all lies about him action so
that has completely fallen apart now
these people come out and they're like
they were going to kill him so that's so
their case is falling apart and the
argument that julian
assange's life would be in any way safe
is completely gone it's almost like
they're and i may be wrong some of these
things may be serendipitous but it's
almost like there are entities that are
making moves to make it harder for
assange for them to convict assad
you know when when the fbi's
star witness
is a convicted pedophile
admitted embezzler
uh who
uh confessed to having made up his
access to both wikileaks and julian
assange
and then in light of an assassination
kidnapping
plan
they have nothing there there's no
there's no case no nothing
it's time for the justice department to
just walk away from this
you know what it has been revealed for
exactly what mike pompeo said it was in
this article yes naked revenge they saw
blood due to vault 7 and they said what
can we use to get him i'm sure a lot of
lawyers looked at it and said we don't
really have a case and they said we
don't care we want to kill him anyway so
if we get him here hey the guards will
fall asleep the cameras will turn off
and he'll hang himself precisely
well thanks a lot garland nixon and john
kiriakou here make sure that you share
and subscribe you subscribe and hit the
little bell so that you get um so that
you get ideally hopefully notifications
you share this on all of your uh
platform all of your um social media
platforms that you um
ask all your friends to subscribe also
and look out for john and i will be
we'll be around for a while peace we're
out good night everybody